<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OK Tested</string>
    <string name="browse_title"><![CDATA[Videos by Your Company]]></string>
    <string name="related_movies">Related Videos</string>
    <string name="grid_view">Grid View</string>
    <string name="error_fragment">Error Fragment</string>
    <string name="personal_settings">Personal Settings</string>
    <string name="watch_trailer_1">Watch trailer</string>
    <string name="watch_trailer_2">FREE</string>
    <string name="rent_1">Rent By Day</string>
    <string name="rent_2">From $1.99</string>
    <string name="buy_1">Buy and Own</string>
    <string name="buy_2">AT $9.99</string>
    <string name="movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="search_results">Search results for \'%1$s\'</string>
    <string name="no_search_results">No search results found for \'%1$s\'</string>
    <string name="catalog_url">http://commondatastorage.googleapis.com/android-tv/android_tv_videos.json</string>
    <string name="prefix_url">http://commondatastorage.googleapis.com/android-tv/Sample%20videos/</string>

    <!-- Error messages -->
    <string name="error_fragment_message">An error occurred</string>
    <string name="dismiss_error">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title_welcome">Welcome to the Leanback Sample</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title_design">Designed for Android TV</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title_simple">Simple to include</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title_project">Check out the Sample Project</string>

    <string name="onboarding_description_welcome">This is the Onboarding Fragment, which runs when the user first opens the app</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_design">The Leanback sample shows how to quickly design apps designed for a 10-foot user interface</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_simple">You can include the Leanback library through gradle in your own apps</string>
    <string name="onboarding_description_project">Are you looking for guidance? This sample is available on GitHub so you can see how we built this.</string>

    <string name="please_check_internet_connection" translatable="false">Please check internet connection</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="dialog_example_title">LogOut?</string>
    <string name="dialog_example_description">This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.
This is a legal and binding agreement between you, the user (“User” or “You”) of the Services, as defined below, and ScoopWhoop Media Private Limited (“ScoopWhoop”) stating the terms that govern Your use of the Site or the Platform, as defined below. You have accepted these Terms of Use, which govern your use of our service. Personally identifying information is subject to our Privacy Policy, the terms of which are incorporated herein. Please review our Privacy Statement to understand our practices. BY ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT, AGREE AND UNDERTAKE TO ABIDE, BE BOUND BY AND ADHERE TO THE TERMS OF USE ("Terms of Use" or "Terms" or "Terms and Conditions" AND IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE, YOU ARE NOT ENTITLED TO AVAIL OF / USE THE SERVICES AND ANY USE THEREAFTER SHALL BE UNAUTHORIZED.
ScoopWhoop provides a personalized subscription services that allows our members to access ScoopWhoop Content streamed over the internet.

1. Description of Service and Acceptance of the Terms of Uses

ScoopWhoop Media Private Limited (ScoopWhoop) ("ScoopWhoop," "we," or "us") provides an online video service offering a selection of shows, movies, clips, and other content (collectively, the "Content"). Our video service, the Content, our player for viewing the Content (the "Video Player") and any other features, tools, materials, or other services (including third party branded services) offered from time to time by ScoopWhoop through a variety of Access Points (defined below) are referred to collectively as the "Services." The term "Access Points" refers to, collectively, the https://ScoopWhoop.com/ website (the "Site"), applications, and other places where any Services are available, including websites and applications of ScoopWhoop third party distribution partners and other websites where users or website operators are permitted to embed or have otherwise licensed the Video Player.

The use of ScoopWhoop Services is available only to persons who can form legally binding contracts under Indian Contract Act, 1872. Persons who are incompetent to contract within the meaning of the Indian Contract Act, 1872 are not eligible to use the Services.

Please note that the availability of, and Your ability to access, the Content or some part of Services, (a) is subject to ScoopWhoop’s sole discretion and/or (b) may be dependent upon Your geographical location and/or (c) is on the condition that not all Content or Services will be available to all viewers. On account of the nature of the Internet, this Site and the Services may also be accessed in various geographical locations; and You hereby agree and acknowledge that You are accessing this Site and using the Services, at Your own risk, choice and initiative and You agree and undertake to ensure that Your use of the Site and the Services complies with all applicable laws including the local laws in Your jurisdiction. Further, such Services and Content may vary from place to place, time to time and device to device and are subject to various parameters such as specifications, device, Internet availability and speed, bandwidth, etc. To facilitate Your viewership and access, the Services can be packaged by ScoopWhoop, at its sole discretion, through different models such as, Content or Services may be accessible free of charge which may include advertisements or commercials.

Use of the Services (including access to the Content) is subject to compliance with these Terms and any end user license agreement that might accompany the applicable Service. Therefore, by visiting the ScoopWhoop Site or using any of the Services through any other Access Point you are agreeing to these Terms.

2. Changes to These Terms

The Terms is subject to revision at any time, as determined by ScoopWhoop, without notice, and any such changes are effective immediately upon being posted on the Website; any use of the Website thereafter will be deemed to be an acceptance of these changes by the User. Users are strongly urged to read this Terms in its entirety and to periodically check this page to understand how modifications or revisions to this policy affects the use of their information. ScoopWhoop shall not be responsible for any User’s failure to remain informed about such changes.

3. Access and Use of the Services

3.1 Age Limitations.

By visiting the Site or using any of the Services, You accept and agree to be bound by these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy and to abide by all applicable laws, rules and regulations. Unless otherwise specified, the Services is available for individuals aged 18 years or older. If You are under the age of 18, You should review these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy with Your parent or legal guardian to make sure that You and Your parent or legal guardian understands and agrees to it on Your behalf and further if required, You shall perform or undertake such activities which will entitle You to enter into a legally binding agreement with ScoopWhoop.

3.2 Your License.

Subject to the terms (including, without limitation, the Your Responsibilities section set forth below), ScoopWhoop grants You a non-exclusive limited, revocable, limited permission to use the Services on the Site for personal, non-commercial purposes during the subsistence of Your Account for the territory of the world or limited territories as applicable in respect of specified.</string>
    <string name="dialog_example_button_positive">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_example_button_negative">No</string>
    <string name="dialog_example_button_toast_positive_clicked">\'Agree\' clicked.</string>
    <string name="dialog_example_button_toast_negative_clicked">\'Disagree\' clicked.</string>

</resources>
